[music]
>> Hey, please subscribe. Thank you.
>> [music]
>> So, I'm here asking you all to let me
know what podcasts you think I should go
on. I've already got a I've already got
a message into um
into uh Grits and Eggs. I've already got
a message into Briana Gray. I've got a
uh Saby said she's going to look and see
if she when she has some time. I've got
a message into Breakthrough News.
Um
However, you know, to be quite honest, I
Who made my outfit?
This is vintage Anthropologie.
>> [laughter]
>> This actually might be vintage Urban
Outfitters.
I don't know if I would produce for
others um because I don't know that I
have the temperament to do the back and
forth.
You know, and the feeling of like
wanting to please somebody it would just
like overwhelm me, I think.
Um so, unless we already had a
relationship and like a a vibration that
we knew was already in alignment, like I
wouldn't I don't know that that would be
for me.
Um
Thank you, Laurel.
Yes, uh Mona, I sent a message out to
Mona as well today, Marquis. Thank you
very much. And um
And you know, I will go on the Joe
Budden podcast. I don't have I got two
friends there. I don't got no beef with
Joe. And and Marco My Hell and Mona are
there. You know, those are my peeps.
Those are my peeps.
But, I'm really excited and I'm really
excited to bring this music to you all.
So, the Sound Sessions tour is going to
be a very different type of interaction
where we're going to be playing the
music, you're going to be listening to
it in community in real time, and we'll
be talking about the songs and what you
got from the songs, and you know, I'll
be bringing to you elements of the
record that you may not have even
noticed, etc. So, really looking forward
to getting to have that exchange with
y'all cuz I feel like we don't get to do
that around music and it's necessary I
feel especially when we're making music
that has levels and layers that need to
get down to our levels and layers.
Oh, Shawn Stockman, I'll hit him up.
I'll hit Shawn. We'll be on a DM. Yep.
Okay, so Crystal, so I'll hit Crystal.
I'll hit Shawn.
Um is Kiki too corporate? Yeah, I think
so.
I don't know that she even handles her
scheduling. And I really try my best to
kind of not have to go through the um
you know, the teams.
>> [laughter]
>> Like I do I don't deal with managers.
Even when I'm even when I'm booking
folks to come on my stuff, I would be
like, "No.
I'm booking with you directly."
So, if anyone has any questions about
the album,
um about my music, ask them now while
I'm here with energy, drinking my tea,
my cinnamon tea.
Mhm.
Do Calvin Angel have guests?
I'm I'm watching Paradise. I just saw
Angel's episode of Paradise. She's so
lovely.
>> [gasps]
>> Pull a Miracle just followed my new
music on Bandcamp. Thank you so much.
Thank you. All right, so we got Calvin,
we got Crystal.
We got Shawn Stockman.
Um
What else?
Whenever y'all ask me where you at, you
sound like an op.
Y'all be having op queries, okay?
Y'all be having op queries.
You can go to amandadeevamusic.com right
now and you can hear some of my music.
You hear my music on here all the time,
cuz I play it in the background.
How long was the process and completion
of the album? I literally finished the
album today.
Um you know, I s-
the the album I had started making it
before I knew I was making an album.
You feel me?
Oh, no, I'm not going to go see Sway.
Last time I Swayed Last time I went to
see Sway,
I was like, you've been Swayed.
Um so, I'm good. Um
let's see.
The ability for you all to take things
personal is fascinating.
I said, when you say such and such, you
sound like an op. If your response is,
I'm not an op, I'm fighting for you,
it's like,
I didn't say you were an op. I said you
sound like an op. Fan, he switched sided
on me, and though he apologized, I never
really got over it.
Um
let's see.
Um who else? Okay, so we said I use
logic.
Um so we said
Oh, so anyways, for the album, I had
started kind of like making it and
hold on, let me block this person. So I
started making it before I knew I was
making an album, because basically I had
started like just tinkering around with
producing. However, I was going to go to
my
normal producer and work on something
together, because my producer is Ray
Angry, and he is my sonic soulmate.
However, his schedule was just so
bonkers that I kind of just kept on
creating, and next thing I knew, I was
like, hold on.
I'm like,
I think I have an album coming together.
And then,
um my
last
like my producer who mixed my last
record that I made back in the day, he
had like commented under one of my
posts. And so I I texted him. I was
like, "Is this still your number?" He
said, "Yeah." And I said, "Wait, do you
still produce?" He was like, I mean, I
was like, "Do you still engineer?" He
was like, "Yeah, I'm actually really
good now." And
so we reconnected and we have been
working together and it's just been such
a dream working with Matt Cody. So shout
out to Matt.
And
you know,
when I say a dream, I want to point out
that things aren't necessarily smooth
and that's what makes it a dream. There
there
Oh, Godfrey. Godfrey, can I come on your
podcast and talk about my new album?
We're in here talking about podcasts I
should go on to talk about my album.
I'm going to text you some of the songs.
Um
and but the best part is when you can
like keep moving, right? When you can
keep moving and when you can listen to
each other and when you don't let ego
get in the way and when you really make
sure that the most paramount thing here
is the art.
And that's what we did and that's what
we're doing. So shout out to the homie
Matt Cody for just being an amazing
brother and engineer
um and friends.
>> [laughter]
>> Like, how about that? Um
Okay, so someone else asked I should sit
with Slink Johnson.
Oh, I like Slink.
I did.
>> [laughter]
>> I [ __ ] with Slink heavy.
I [ __ ] with Slink heavy. Let me get a
notepad. Hold on.
Okay, I'm back.
All right.
So, we said Crystal's couch.
I'm going to DM Slink.
We said Kev and Angela.
I'm going to DM them. Someone asked me
about Angela Yee and um
she actually just texted me and said
she'd love to have me on, so we're going
to figure that out.
I've done Deonna's podcast before and it
was very good. People loved it. So, I
already hit him, so we'll see if he hits
me back. Um
I'm missing somebody. Oh, y'all said
Shawn Stockman.
Um Godfrey, you did say Godfrey, you did
say Godfrey. Yep, so let me hit Godfrey.
Um
yep, I put Kev and Angel. So,
Wisdom Wednesday.
Cam on fourth and one, but I know you
ain't going to do it. I just rock with
both of y'all.
Who's Cam on fourth and one?
Is that Cam Newton?
I don't know that that would be valuable
for either of us.
Thank you 612 MJ.
Oh, Cam'ron or Cam Newton?
Oh, Cam Newton. Okay.
Uh no no, I was like, I think they mean
the other Cam. I think they mean the
other Cam. Um
All right.
So, so these are the podcasts that y'all
listening to.
Good. Someone said no on Cam Newton,
he'd be so intimidated. I genuinely
don't know anything about Cam Newton
other than the hats and that before he
was wearing the hats, he was one of the
finest men alive.
Yeah.
Like
Like I was at a wedding and the woman
sitting next to me, somehow Cam Newton
came up and she was like clowning him
and um she was like, "I just can't get
with the hats, etc." And I was like,
"Let it be known that Cam is fine as
hell." Would I sit down with Snoop?
Only I mean the only way I would sit
down with Snoop is he knows he's going
to hear my mouth.
Calvin?
Cordarrelle?
Broaddus?
He knows he's going to hear about how
disappointed I am in him.
>> [music]
[music]